

# **Maciej Hnat**

Senior Frontend Developer

Phone: +48 500 767 393 Email: maciekhnat@gmail.com

LinkedIn: /in/maciej-hnat/ GitHub: /mecies

Website: https://maciejhnat.dev/

Senior Frontend Developer with 4 years of experience building engaging web applications using React and Vue. I specialize in creating user-friendly interfaces, optimizing website performance, and implementing responsive designs. My dedication to continuous learning and improvement ensures high-quality results that exceed client expectations. With leadership experience in managing and mentoring small frontend teams, I am committed to achieving project goals on time and on budget.

## **Skills**

#### **Technologies**

| React.js                   | Vue.js | TypeScript   | Next.js            | Nuxt    | t.js Ga | tsby.js    | HTML5  | CSS3       |
|----------------------------|--------|--------------|--------------------|---------|---------|------------|--------|------------|
| JavaScript ES6 React Query |        |              | Apollo GraphQL Rec |         | Redux   | SASS Style |        | Components |
| Tailwind CS                | S Mate | erial UI Sto | orybook            | Storybl | ok Je:  | st Play    | wright | Cypress    |
| Node.js GraphQL            |        | WebSocke     | ets Web            | RTC     | Prisma  | PostgreSQL |        | MongoDB    |

#### Languages

Polish native English fluent

## **Work experience**

## **Senior Frontend Developer & Tech Lead**

July 2021 - now

#### **Swapcard**

- Developing and maintaining an all-in-one platform for creating virtual events.
- Developing and maintaining a design system for the company.
- Developing a professional live streaming studio application from scratch.
- Introducing frontend-centric e2e tests, preventing regression in SEO, a11y, and SSR.
- Leading a team of 4 developers.
- Mentoring and coaching junior developers.

**Technologies:** React.js, Next.js, TypeScript, Styled Components, Storybook, Apollo GraphQL, GraphQL, WebSockets, WebRTC, Jest, Cypress, Playwright, ESLint, Prettier, Node.js, Yarn, Lerna

### **Senior Frontend Developer**

May 2022 - now

Xfive · Part-time

- Developing a platform that eases the process of translating ancient buddhist texts.
- Working closely with the client to deliver a tailor-made solution to their domain needs.
- Leading a team of 2 frontend developers.

**Technologies:** React.js, Next.js, React Query, TypeScript, Styled Components, SASS, Jest, ESLint, Prettier, Node.js, Yarn

### **Frontend Developer**

October 2020 - July 2021

Infermedica

- Developing an Al-powered medical diagnosis platform for doctors and patients.
- Developing and maintaining a design system for the company.
- Maintaining a legacy medical application and delivering it to the clients.
- Maintaining an existing static marketing website and creating a new one with CMS.

**Technologies:** Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Svelte, AngularJS, Django, TypeScript, JavaScript ES6, SASS, Storybook, Storyblok, Jest, ESLint, Prettier, npm

## **Junior Frontend Developer**

February 2020 - October 2020

Monterail

- Developing a journey planner and online booking platform for European travel.
- Developing an online pharmacy platform for the US market.
- Developing an internal e-learning platform for the company.
- Developing an internal employee growth framework platform for the company.
- Working in multiple teams of 1-5 frontend developers on multiple projects.

**Technologies:** Vue.js, React.js, Next.js, Nuxt.js, Redux, TypeScript, SASS, Styled Components, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, Jest, ESLint, Prettier, Node.js, npm, Yarn

## **Education**

#### **Business Informatics**

October 2017 - July 2020

**Wroclaw University of Economics** 

Bachelor's degree. Specialization in system analysis and design.

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process.